Guide to the Edward Bradford Titchener papers,1887-1940.
Titchener, Edward Bradford papers, 1887-1940
- Correspondence
  - Circular letter from Carl Murchison, 12/10/26 (Box 7)
  - W. Norman Brown to EBT, 12/10/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford, 12/13/26 (Box 7)
  - Livingston Farrand to EBT, 12/14/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to The Corner Book Store, 12/16/26 (Box 7)
  - Add. EBT to Forrest L. Dimmick, 12/17/26 (Box 7)
  - Charles Myers to EBT, 12/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Dr.Lillian A. Phelps, 12/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Raphael C. McCarthy, 12/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT toT. L. Elder, 12/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 12/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 12/17/26 (Box 7)
  - Durbar, Nutter and McClennen to EBT, 12/17/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 12/23/26 (Box 7)
  - EBT to Ogden, 1/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Duribar, Nutter and McClennen, 1/10/27 (Box 8)
  - Entitled and unsigned, 1/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dean S. W. Reaves, 1/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 1/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 1/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor C. A. Ruckmick, 1/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT: to Professor H. G. Bishop, 1/12/27 (Box 8)
  - * insertions made because add. material receive. See Accession Sheets. (Box 8)
  - EBT to Miss Lillian Hatfield, 1/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 1/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 1/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. A. Poynder, 1/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 1/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 1/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor W. Heinrich, 1/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 1/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. M. Ogden, 1/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 1/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder, 1/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 1/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to B. A. Tsanoff, 1/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. D. Powers, 1/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 1/17/27 (Box 8)
  - S. Feldman to EBT, 1/19/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith, 1/19/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 1/19/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The President of Wells College, 1/19/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor M. G. Seheck, 1/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Ferriberger, 1/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. L. J. O'Rourcke, 1/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 1/25/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to the Macmillan Company, 1/27/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 1/27/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. H. C. Sya, 1/27/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to N. C. Meier, 1/27/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 1/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. Rose S. Malmud, 1/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Duribar Nutter and McClennen, 2/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 2/3/27 (Box 8)
  - Draft of plans for a new Journal of General Psychology, 2/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Murchison, 2/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 2/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor M. L. Beymert, 2/4/27 (Box 8)
  - Jaxnes Baldwin to EBT, 2/5/27 (Box 8)
  - Ferriberger to EBT, 2/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to A. Barr Gray, 2/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Ferriberger, 2/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. L. Hollingsworth, 2/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. Elmer Culler, 2/8/27 (Box 8)
  - Hoisington to EBT, 2/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Lincoln E. Patterson, 2/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor Foster Boswell, 2/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Miss Frances Wells, 2/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 2/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. H. B. Davies, 2/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor F. L. Dimmick, 2/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. Edgar J. Banks, 2/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 2/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to George Kreezer, 2/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence Hazzard, 2/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor F. L. Dimmick, 2/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Murchison, 2/11/27 (Box 8)
  - draft of plans for a new Journal of General Psychology, 2/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor Knight Dunlop, 2/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 2/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor H. S. Langfeld, 2/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Secretary of the Board of Fellowships, 2/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. R. Smith, 2/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 2/24/27 (Box 8)
  - Carl Murchison to EBT, 2/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor D. C. Roger, 2/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Miss Prances Wells, 2/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. D. Powers, 2/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Hynson Westcott and Dunning, 2/25/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor S. W. Fernberger, 2/15/27 (Box 8)
  - Fernberger to EBT, 2/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 2/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor W. A. Garrison, 2/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. S. Feldman, 2/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 2/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 2/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to New York Life Insurance Co., 2/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 2/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 2/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 2/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Horiguehi, 2/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 2/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mr.. F. H. Ward, 2/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor Edna Winters, 2/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Alien Wilber, 2/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Albert Teachers' Agency, 2/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 2/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 2/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Miss Prances Wells, 2/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Murchison, 2/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 2/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 2/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EEC to Hynson Westcott and Dunning, 2/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Edgar J. Banks, 2/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 2/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 2/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to A. Bar Gray, 2/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Gardner Well, 2/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 2/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 2/28/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 2/28/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 3/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 3/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 3/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 3/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. B. Miner, 3/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor R. A. Tsanoff, 3/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 3/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 3/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. L. F. Bixley, 3/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. S. Feldman, 3/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. S. Langfeld, 3/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mansbach Cigar Co., 3/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/7/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 3/7/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 3/7/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 3/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Max Meyer, 3/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor G. Heyroans, 3/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 3/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 3/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Benjamen Gravely, 3/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 3/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. B. Hoisington, 3/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Associated School services, Chariottesville, Va., 3/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor E. G. Boring, 3/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Helen Lynd, 3/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Reyraert, 3/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. S. Peldman, 3/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor Carl Murchison, 3/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence Hazzard, 3/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dr. S. Feldman, 3/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor J. P. Nafe, 3/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Bpring, 3/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mr.. F. H. Ward, 3/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor R. A. Tsanoff, 3/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence Haaaard, 3/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 3/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mr.. Maslow, 3/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor M. A. Caldwell, 3/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor S. W. Fernberger, 3/15/27 (Box 8)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 3/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 3/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to B. H. Blacknell, 3/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Abel, 3/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to P. H. Ward, 3/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Alien and Unwin, Ltd, 3/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Lucus Bros., 3/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. B. Hoisington, 3/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 3/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Elizabeth B. Young, 3/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to James P. Porter, 3/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 3/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. A. Tsanoff, 3/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 3/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. D. Powers, 3/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Percy Hughes, 3/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to George D. Ferguson, Jr., 3/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 3/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. R. Abdrus, 3/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 3/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Louise Mae Dawley, 3/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. T. Nielson, 3/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dean of the Graduate School, 3/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Miss E. R. Moul, 3/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to National Teachers Agency, 3/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L.,Reymert, 3/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to. L. N. Wilson, 3/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. A. Tsanoff, 3/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 3/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence, 3/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 3/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Robinson and Carpenter, 3/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to D. Griffin, 3/25/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. Feldman, 3/25/27 (Box 8)
  - Instructions by EBT, 3/25/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, Esq., 3/28/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Gardner Wells, 3/28/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 3/28/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 3/28/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 3/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBP to Howland Wood, 3/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Kodak Egypt Co, 3/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. A. Tsanoff, 3/29/27 (Box 8)
  - Gardner Wens to EBT, 3/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E.G. Boring, 3/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. R. Garvey, 3/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to A. S. Wilber, 3/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Percy Hughes, 3/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Stumpf, 3/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. D. Powers, 3/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to W. R. Whitney, 3/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Gardner Wells, 3/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 3/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to D. C. Rogers, 3/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 3/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L.R. Andrews, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to American College Bureau, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT (secretary) to American Philosophical Society, 4/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to W. S. Foster, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to ELeonore Wundt, 4/l/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 4/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Walter F. Prince, 4/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to A. C. Watson, 4/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 4/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The Macraillan Company, 4/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 4/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. Lovell Bixfcy, 4/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 4/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mrs. F. Lovell Bixbgr, 4/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mrs. Rogers, 4/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. A. Tsanoff, 4/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Powers, 4/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. Fred Howse, Esq., 4/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to W. D. Lighthall, 4/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Earl D. Bond, 4/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 4/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Baldwin, 4/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. Feldman, 4/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 4/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Giorgio Le Grass!, 4/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Helder, 4/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, 4/l5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Lillian Hatfield, 4/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Psychological Review Co., 4/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi, 4/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Robert Matheson, 4/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 4/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Curtice Hithcock, 4/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to W. B. Pillsbury, 4/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mrs. Rogers, 4/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mrs. P. Lovell Bixby, 4/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mrs. Lovell, 4/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Wold ? (Weld), 4/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Whitney, 4/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Alien Johnson, 5/2/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Charles W. Frank, 5/2/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 5/2/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 5/2/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Ferriberger, 5/2/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 5/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 5/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Walter Franklin Pierce, 5/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Psychology Foundation, 5/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. McKeen Cattell, 5/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, Esq., 5/3/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. M. Terkes, 5/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. L. Diramick, 5/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to A. J. Snow, 5/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. Q. Boring, 5/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. T. Newell, 5/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 5/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to P. L. Dimmick, 5/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. M. Halverson, 5/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. A. WOHL, 5/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Perriberger, 5/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 5/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H£ G. Bishop, 5/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dean of the Graduate School, 5/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 5/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dean of the College of Arts and Sciences, 5/5/27 (Box 8)
  - R. A. Tsanoff to EBT, 5/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 5/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Latham, 5/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 5/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 5/9/27 (Box 8)
  - Martin L. Reymert to EBT, 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. T. Newell, 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Postmaster, San Francisco, California., 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Martin L. Reymert, 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. L. Bixby, 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. G. Bishop, 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 5/10/27 (Box 8)
  - E. E. Ferris to EBT, 5/11/27 (Box 8)
  - H. S. Langfeld to EBT (encl.), 5/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dean of the Graduate School, 5/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to George 0. Ferguson, Jr., 5/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, Esq., 5/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. C. Stevens, 5/11/27 (Box 8)
  - S. W. Fernberger to EBT, 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - Carl Murchison to EBT, 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to A. N. Gibb, 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The Bell and Howell Co., 5/12/27 (Box 8)
  - John P, Nafe to EBT, 5/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Rowland Wofcd, 5/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to K. Koffka, 5/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to W. D. McELwee, 5/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Arthur N. Gibb, 5/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to U. S. Fidelity and Guarantee Co., 5/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mansbach Cigar Co., 5/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to 8. W. Fernberger, 5/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 5/26/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to 0. M. Braxiner, 5/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 5/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi (2 copies), 5/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Enid C. Straw, 5/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to T. H. Elder, 5/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Raymond Dodge, 5/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. N. Wilson, 5/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 5/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Miss R. S. Malaod, 5/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Otto Klem, 5/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mrs.. F. W. Hazzard, 5/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. B. Hoisington, 5/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. R. B. Willis, 5/18/27 (Box 8)
  - Bixby to EBT, 5/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to L. B. Hoisington, 5/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder, 5/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Dean of the Graduate School, 5/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Miss Frances Wells, 5/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 5/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence Romig, 5/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 5/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The President, Wells College., 5/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 5/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Board of Education of the District of Columbia, 5/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Raymert, 5/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The Macmillan Company, 5/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. G. Bishop, 5/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. Baldwin, 5/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Ferriberger, 5/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 5/25/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to 0. M. Brauner, 5/25/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mrs. Florence Hazzard, 5/26/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, Esq, 5/26/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence L. Goodenough, 5/26/27 (Box 8)
  - Carl Murchison to EBT, 5/28/27 (Box 8)
  - George W. Cavanaugh to EBT, 5/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 5/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguehi, 5/30/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 5/30/27 (Box 8)
  - Junichiro Horiguehi to EBT, 5/31/27 (Box 8)
  - Junichiro Horiguehi to EBT (and end.), 5/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murdjison, 5/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. Feldman, 5/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to George W. Cavanaugh, 5/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 5/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. P. Powers, 5/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi, 5/31/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi (2 copies), 6/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Philip Johnson, 6/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. L. Dimmick, 6/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F (S. Feldman), 6/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. T. lanes, 6/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. H. Stoelting, 6/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 6/2/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. W. Cavanatigh, 6/2/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. W. Sailor, 6/2/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. M. Yerkes, 6/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl MureMson, 6/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence L. Goodenough, 6/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Fuertes, 6/4/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. E. Bierly, 6/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to D. C. Rogers, 6/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. George Scheck, 6/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Henry R. Head, 6/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Rowland Wood, 6/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 6/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mr.. E. Barrett, 6/7/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 6/7/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 6/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. H. Gault, 6/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 6/9/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 6/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mark Uddell, 6/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 6/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 6/10/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. H. StoaLtisg, 6/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder, 6/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. G. Boring, 6/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to HowlaiKi Wood, 6/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Powers, 6/13/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Horiguchi, 6/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The Comptroller (Cornell University), 6/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 6/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 6/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Perriberger, 6/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Rotschild (Ithaca), 6/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 6/16/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carl Murchison, 6/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. S. Langfeld, 6/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to A. Schinz, 6/17/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. Q. Scheck, 6/19/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to D. M. Garrison, 6/17/27 (Box 8)
  - Helen X. H. to EBT, 6/18/27 (Box 8)
  - Florence E. Romig to EBT, 6/19/27 (Box 8)
  - C. Stumpf to EBT (German, with translation), 6/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 6/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Carney Landis, 6/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. G. Bishop, 6/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence E. Romig, 6/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence E. Romig, 6/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Helen, 6/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Ferriberger, 6/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Professor R. Matheson, 6/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mansbach Cigar Co., 6/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Harriet C. Marble, 6/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Harriet C. Marble, 6/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 6/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self., ESQ., 6/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. W. Fernberger, 6/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. C. Scheck, 6/22/27 (Box 8)
  - Junichiro Horiguchi to BBT, 6/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. Weld, 6/23/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to MR.. J. Baldwin, 6/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to President (Livingston Farrand), 6/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The President (Cornell), 6/24/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Harriet C. Marbel, 6/27/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. 0. Smith, 6/27/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. C. Warren, 6/27/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mansbach Cigar Co., 6/27/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to W. D. McElwee, 6/28/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to R. A. Heggie and Bro. Co., 6/28/27 (Box 8)
  - BBT to C. H. Stoelting, 6/28/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. J. Rumsey, 6/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Buchard-Chung Gustav FOCK, 6/29/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. J. Bool, 6/29/27 (Box 8)
  - Bill from Cornell Co-operative Society, 6/30/27 (Box 8)
  - W. D. McElwee to EBT, 7/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Howland Wood, 7/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Charles H. Brooks, 7/1/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 7/1/27 (Box 8)
  - Christine Ladd-Franklin to EBT (with Encl.), 7/4/27 (Box 8)
  - J. P. Nafe to EBT, 7/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to 3. H. Self, Esq., 7/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to W. H. McElwee, 7/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. Stump f, 7/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Harriet C. Marble, 7/5/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Christine Ladd-Franklin, 7/6/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 7/6/27 (Box 8)
  - J. Baldwin to EBT, 7/7/27 (Box 8)
  - Christine Ladd-Franklin to EBT (postcard), 7/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder, 7/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. G. Bishop, 7/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Reymert, 7/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Milwaukee Public Library, 7/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to B. H. Blackwell, 7/8/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Harriet C. Marble, 7/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Nafe, 7/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to F. H. Ward, 7/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to G. T. Lines, 7/11/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Edward T. Newell, 7/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Norma V. Scheldemann, 7/12/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi, 7/12/27 (Box 8)
  - Horace B. English to EBT, 7/14/27 (Box 8)
  - Christine Ladd-Franklin to EBT, 7/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to B. B. Bassett, 7/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to S. H. Self, Esq., 7/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Christine Ladd-Franklin, 7/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to E. T. Newell, 7/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Florence Chandler, 7/14/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to H. G. Bishop, 7/15/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder (with End.), 7/15/27 (Box 8)
  - Harriet G. Marble to EBT, 7/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. P. Guilford (orig.and carbon), 7/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Christine Ladd-Franklin, 7/18/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. J. Zigler, 7/19/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Laurance L. Clough, 7/19/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to The Prudential Committee, Wittenberg College, 7/20/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Thomas J. Reilly, 7/20/27 (Box 8)
  - Martin L. Haymert to EBT (with Encl.), 7/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Otto T. Bannard, 7/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to C. A. Ruckmick, 7/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to T. L. Elder, 7/21/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Horace B. English, 7/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to Mr.. J. Baldwin, 7/22/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to J. Horiguchi (2 copies), 7/25/27 (Box 8)
  - EBT to M. L. Reywert, 7/25/27 (Box 8)
  - Wm. A. Hammond to Mrs.. T., encl. copy of resolutions of Bd. Tr. and Faculty on death of EBT., 10/31/27 (Box 8)
  - R. A. Tsanoff to Mrs. Titchener, 12/23/27 (Box 8)
  - Alice Dean to H. P. Weld, 12/29/27 (Box 8)
  - Alice Dean to Mrs. Titchener {with End.), 12/29/27 (Box 8)
  - Biographical Sketch, 1927? (Box 8)
  - Undated: (Box 8)
  - Robt. M. Yerkes to EBT, no date (Box 8)
  - Robt. M. Terkes to EBT, no date (Box 8)
- Photos, plaque, manuscript by Alma M(ary) Bowman (Box 9)
- Correspondence, printed material received since 1966 (Box 10)
- Misc. printed material and small notebooks (Box 11)
- Additional correspondence received from Mrs.. T. Baird (Box 12)
- E.B.T.' s Annual Reports to Pres. J.G. Schurman, c. 1896-97, 1901-02 to 1926-27 (Box 13)
- Original drawings for E.B.T.'s Manual (Box 14)
- Pamphlets (reprints of E.B.T.'s articles)
  - "The Problems of Experimental Psychology," American Journal of Psychology, April 7, 1905 (Box 15)
  - "The Problems of Experimental Psychology," American Journal of Psychology, April 1905 (Box 15)
  - "A Bibliography of the Scientific Writings of Wilhelm Wundt," American Journal of Psychology, October 1908 (Box 15)
  - "A Demonstrational Color-Pyramid," American Journal of Psychology, January 1909 (Box 15)
  - "The Psychophysics of Climate," American Journal of Psychology, January 1909 (Box 15)
  - "Some New Apparatus," American Journal of Psychology, April 1909 (Box 15)